在这个视频里，
In this video,
让我们开始在实践中应用盒子模型
let's start applying the box model in practice
尤其是边距和填充。
and in particular margins and paddings.
让我们从填充和一个伟大的候选人开始
And let's start with padding and one great candidate
添加一些填充是这里的标题元素，
for adding some padding is this header element here,
它具有这种背景颜色。
which has this background color.
所以一个有背景颜色的元素，
So an element which has background color,
总是可以使用一些填充来创造一些空间
can always use some padding in order to create some space
在元素的内容和外部之间。
between the content and the outside of an element.
那是因为记住填充基本上只是空间
That's because remember padding is basically just space
那是元素的内部。
that is inside of the element.
所以这个元素被称为主标题，
So this element is called the main header,
我想我们在这里的某个地方有它
and I think we have it somewhere down here
确实在这里。
and indeed here it is.
现在实际上，我想做的是把这段代码放到这里，
Now actually, what I want to do is to take this code here,
这是用于这些盒子的，并将其放在顶部。
which is for these boxes and put it a bit more to the top.
所以我喜欢有，像这些大的水平盒子，
So I like to have, like these big level boxes,
所以包含多个子元素的盒子
so boxes that contain multiple child elements
或更多在顶部。
or more at the top.
好的。
All right.
所以这里的这个标题是这些大盒子中的第一个。
So this header here is kind of the first of these big boxes.
所以我会把它放在身体后面。
And so I will put it here right after the body.
好的。
All right.
但是现在让我们从添加一些填充开始。
But now let's start by adding some padding.
所以我们使用填充，一个属性，
So we use the padding, a property,
然后我们需要指定一些长度。
and then we need to specify some length.
所以让我们使用 20 像素。
So let's use 20 pixels.
所以像素与我们使用的单位完全相同
And so pixels is exactly the same unit that we also used
用于边框宽度，也用于字体大小。
for the border width, and also for font sizes.
记住？
Remember?
那么让我们看看它是什么样子的。
So let's see what that looks like.
事实上，我们现在得到了一些新的空间
And indeed, we now got ourselves some new space that is
在内容之间，所以在这一切之间，
between the content, so between all of this,
当然还有元素的外部。
and of course the outside of the element.
现在看起来这里的空间和这里一样。
Now it looks like the space here is the same as here.
所以它是 20 像素，但是这里有更多的空间。
So it's 20 pixels, but then here there's a lot more space.
因此，让我们右键单击此元素并检查。
So let's right click here on this element and inspect.
所以在这里你看到了原因。
And so here you see the reason for that.
所以当我们将鼠标悬停在一个元素上时，
So when we hover over an element,
我们实际上得到了那个元素的边距。
we actually get the margin off that element.
这就是那个红色或橙色的覆盖层。现在对吗？
And so that is that red or that orange overlay. Now right?
现在标题本身，你看到那里的绿色空间，
And now the header itself, you see the green space there,
那是填充。
that is the padding.
好的。
Okay.
所以你会看到事实上，
So you'll see that in fact,
填充物在盒子周围
the padding goes all around the box
或在盒子内部的所有周围
or all around the inside of the box
而且到处都是20像素。
00:02:39,130​​ --> 00:02:39,963
好的。
and it is really 20 pixels everywhere.
Okay.
所以我们稍后会在这里修复这个边距
So we will fix this margin here in a second
到那时，一切都会变得有意义。
and by then, everything will make sense.
好的。
Okay.
现在实际上在风格上，
Now actually down here in the styles,
我们可以看到盒子模型。
we can see the box model.
对？
Right?
所以在这里我们确实看到了，
And so here we see that indeed,
到处都有 20 的填充，所以在所有四个边上。
there is padding of 20 everywhere, so on all four sides.
所以这里的这个其实就是宽度和高度，
So this one here is actually the width and height,
然后是填充，然后是边框，然后是边距。
then the padding, then the border and then the margin.
所以对于每个元素，
So for each element,
有一个完整的盒子模型表示
there is a complete representation of the box model
就在开发工具中
right here in the dev tools
很多时候这非常有帮助。
and many times this is extremely helpful.
所以我们现在肯定会使用它，稍后再使用。
So we will use this now for sure, a bit later.
现在这里的填充确实创建了相同的填充
Now this padding here does create the same padding
在盒子的所有四个侧面。
on all four sides of the box.
但是如果我们想创建不同的填充
But if we wanted to create different paddings
在不同的方面，我们也可以很容易地做到这一点。
on different sides, we can do that also just very easily.
So let's say we want a different paddings
所以假设我们想要一个不同的填充
在左边和右边。
at the left and right.
所以我们可以说，例如，
So we can say for example,
左右各 40 像素。
40 pixels on the left and on the right.
所以这实际上是一回事
And so this is in fact exactly the same thing
与边界一样。
as with the border.
所以记住边界，
So remember with the border,
我们还有边框顶部、边框底部、左侧和右侧。
we also have border top, border bottom, left, and right.
好的。
Okay.
而现在，确实，
And now indeed,
左侧的空间比
there's a lot more space here on the left side than
在底部。
on the bottom.
右边也是一样，
And the same here on the right side,
即使我们无法从内容上真正看到它，
even though we cannot really see it by the content,
但我们可以使用开发工具在这里看到它。对？
but we can see it here using the dev tools. Right?
所以你在右边看到，
So you see that here on the right,
我们在左边有 40、40 个，然后在顶部和底部有 20 个。
we have 40, 40 on the left and then 20 on top and on bottom.
好的。
All right.
但是现在，我们实际上可以用更好的方式来写这个
But now, we can actually write this in an even better way
再次使用一种叫做速记的东西。
by using something called a shorthand once again.
因此，当我们指定多个值时，总是简写
So a shorthand is always when we specify multiple values
这里是一处房产。
here for one property.
所以对于填充，我们可以做的是，
So for padding, what we can do is to,
而不是仅仅指定一个值，
instead of just specifying one value,
然后在所有四个站点上都是相同的，
which will then be the same on all four sites,
我们可以指定两个值。
we can specify two values.
如果我们这样做，那么第一个值将是填充
And if we do that, then the first value will be padding
在顶部和底部。
on the top and bottom.
第二个值将在左侧填充
And the second value will be padding on the left
和右侧。
and right side.
所以要达到和以前一样的结果，
So to achieve the same result as before,
我们会说 20 像素和 40 像素。
we would say 20 pixels and 40 pixels.
所以如果我们现在在这里删除这句话，像这样，
And so if we now removed this quote here, like this,
使用注释，那么我们的结果还是一样的。
using a comment, then our result is still the same.
好的。
Okay.
所以我们用这个速记在顶部和底部加20，
So we use this shorthand to add 20 to top and bottom,
和 40 左右。
and 40 to left and right.
这样我们就不必写所有这些
And this way we don't have to write all of these
这里有不同的代码行。
different lines of codes here.
我们可以一口气做完。
We can just do it all in one go.
接下来，让我们玩一点边距。
Next up, let's play a little bit with margins.
请记住，边距基本上是空格
And remember that margins are basically spaces
元素之间。
between elements.
所以现在让我们在 LI 元素之间添加一些空间。
So let's now add some space between the LI elements.
所以这里的这些，
So these ones here,
你看到他们非常接近
you see that they're very close together
而且看起来不太好。
and it doesn't look nice.
因此我们可以在底部添加一些边距
And therefore we can add some margin to the bottom
这些元素中的每一个。
of each of these elements.
所以这里的某个地方，一定有，
So somewhere down here, there must,
所以已经有了LI，
so there is the LI already,
所以我们不需要一遍又一遍地选择它。
so we don't need to select it over and over again.
我们只是写在这里，在相同的规则内。
We just write it here, inside the same rule.
所以让我们说底部的边距，
And so let's say margin to the bottom,
10 像素。
10 pixels.
所以现在看起来确实好多了，对吧？
And so now that does look a lot better, right?
让我们在这里选择它。
Let's select this here.
确实，
And indeed,
我们得到 10 个像素
we get 10 pixels
在他们每个人的边缘底部。
at the margin bottom on each of them.
滚动到最后一个，
Just scroll to the last one,
因为现在我想给你看一些东西。
because now I want to show you something.
所以通常在最后一个列表项中，
So usually in the last list item,
我们不想有任何空间
we don't want to have any space
因为我们实际上只想要项目之间的空间，
because we actually only want space between the items,
但不是在项目的末尾。
but not at the end of the items.
所以再一次，少一个不应该有任何空间。
So again, the less one should not have any space.
所以让我们为此使用一个技巧，
And so let's use a trick for that,
这实际上是我们之前学到的东西。
which is actually something that we learned before.
所以我们可以说LI，然后是last-child。
So we can say LI, and then last-child.
然后在这里，我们基本上重置了我们刚刚所做的。
And then here, we basically reset what we just did.
所以我们说边距底部并将其设置为零。
So we say margin bottom and set it to zero.
每当我们使用零时，我们不指定任何单位。
And whenever we use zero, we do not specify any unit.
好的？
Okay?
所以我们只说零，然后它将覆盖它。
So we just say zero and that will then override it.
现在我们以前在这里的空间应该消失了。
And now that space that we had here before should be gone.
所以你会看到这个没有边距，但是在它之前的那个，
So you'll see this one has no margin, but the one before it,
底部确实有这 10 个像素。
that does have these 10 pixels at the bottom.
不错，很美
Nice, that's beautiful.
我们现在将继续增加越来越多的利润
And we will now keep adding more and more margins
和填充到我们所有的元素。
and paddings to all of our elements.
但在我们这样做之前，
But before we do that,
我们实际上应该做一些称为全局重置的事情。
we should actually do something called a global reset.
因此，如果您在这里查看我们的页面，
So if you take a look at our page here,
让我们关闭它，然后你会注意到，
and let's close this, then you notice that,
这里其实已经有很多空间了吧？
there are actually already a lot of spaces here, right?
所以这里的 H2 元素周围有空间，
So there's space around this H2 element here,
段落之间，
between the paragraphs,
同样在这里，正如我们在使用开发工具之前所看到的，
also here, as we saw before using the dev tools,
这个H1的顶部和底部有很多余量。
there was a lot of margin on the top and bottom of this H1.
并拥有所有这些默认边距和填充，
And having all of these default margins and paddings,
使我们很难为页面设置样式。
makes it quite hard for us to style our page.
所以我们要做的是重置所有这些边距
So what we want to do is to reset all those margins
和填充，基本上将它们设置为零。
and paddings, and basically set them to zero.
那么您认为我们如何做到这一点？
So how do you think we can do that?
你认为我们应该使用继承吗？
Do you think we should use inheritance?
那么你认为margin和padding会被继承吗
So do you think that margin and padding get inherited
从一个元素到另一个元素？
from one element to the other?
好吧，让我们测试并将边距设置为零。
Well, let's test and set the margin to zero.
那么让我们看看。
So let's see.
好吧，实际上确实发生了一些变化。
And well, something actually did change.
所以身体失去了它所拥有的边缘。
So the body lost the margin that it had.
所以现在一切都像是粘在了这里的边界上。
So now everything is really like glued to the border here.
所以到视口的边界，所以浏览器本身，
So to the border of the viewport, so the browser itself,
但并非所有元素都失去了边距，对吧？
but not all the elements lost its margin, right?
所以这不是真正要走的路
And so this is not really the way to go
因为边距不是与文本相关的属性，
because margin is not a property that is related to text,
因此它不是可以继承的属性
and therefore it's not a property that gets inherited
从父元素到子元素。
from parents to child elements.
相反，如果我们想要应用边距
Instead if we want the margin to be applied
到每一个元素，然后为此，
to every single element, then for that,
我们可以使用通用选择器。
we can use the universal selector.
所以边距设置为零，填充设置为零。
So margin set to zero and padding set to zero.
现在这正是我们正在寻找的结果。
And now this is exactly the result that we were looking for.
所以现在所有的默认空间都消失了
So now all the default spaces are gone
我们可以随意格式化我们的页面。
and we are free to format our page as we wish.
在这里做这样的事情，
And doing something like this here,
所以这种全局重置非常普遍。
so this kind of global reset is extremely common.
所以这通常是我做的第一件事
So this is usually the very first thing that I do
每当我开始任何新项目时。
whenever I start any new project.
还要记住，这里的边距和填充
And also keep in mind that, this margin and padding here
非常容易被覆盖。
are extremely easy to overwrite.
所以所有其他选择器实际上都会覆盖
So every other selector will actually overwrite
这个通用选择器。
this universal selector.
事实上，我们可以在主标题中看到，
And in fact, we can see that right here in the main header,
我们确实指定了一些填充，
where we did specify some padding,
所以当然它在这里仍然可见。
and so of course it is still visible here.
好的。
Okay.
所以再一次，这个类选择器在这里
So once again, this class selector here
具有比全局选择器更高的优先级。
has a higher priority than the global selector.
用更多的技术术语来说，
And in more technical terms,
我们说通用选择器
we say that the universal selector
特异性为零，
has a specificity of zero,
这就是 VS 代码在此工具提示中向我们展示的内容。
which is what VS code shows us here, in this tool tip.
而另一方面，
While on the other hand,
这里的这个选择器确实在这些地方之一。
this selector here does have the one in one of these places.
所以这个更具体。
So this one is more specific.
它具有更高的优先级，
It has a higher priority,
因此填充确实被应用。
and therefore the padding does get applied.
在此列表中也是如此。
And the same is true also right here in this list.
所以在这里我们也应该已经有了 10 个像素
So here we also, already should have the 10 pixels
我们之前指定的。
that we just specified previously.
好的。
Okay.
现在有了这个重置，
And now with this reset in place,
现在添加我们的自定义空间非常容易
it is extremely easy to now add our custom spaces
并让这个页面看起来真的很设计。
and to make this page really look designed.
既然我们已经到了，
And since we're already here,
让我们从 &lt;aside&gt; 开始。
let's actually start here with the &lt;aside&gt;
或继续在这里。
or keep going here.
因为再一次，
Because once again,
这是具有背景颜色的元素之一。
this is one of the elements which has a background color.
所以为了创造一些空间，
And so therefore in order to create some space,
我们应该使用填充，否则，
we should use padding because, otherwise,
这里的边框真的粘在了内容上。
this border here is really glued to the content.
所以这不是我们想要的。
So that's not what we want.
所以让我们说填充50像素的顶部
So let's say padding top of 50 pixels
并且填充底部也是 50 像素，
and padding bottom of also 50 pixels,
让我们给它一个保存，看起来好多了。
let's give it a save and that looks a lot better.
所以现在我们把左边和右边都设为零，
So for now we're leaving left and right side at zero,
我们稍后会解决这个问题。
and we will fix that a bit later.
那么我们怎么能在这里写这个，
So how could we write this here,
实际上以更好的方式？
actually in a bit better way?
好吧，我希望你猜到了。
Well, I hope you guessed it.
答案是使用速记。
And the answer would be to use the shorthand.
所以只需在顶部和底部填充，
So just padding at the top and bottom,
这是 50 像素的第一个值
which is the first value of 50 pixels
第二个值是我们想要零的左右。
and the second value is left and right where we want zero.
现在，就是这样。
Now, that's it.
所以把这个拿出来，
So take this out,
给它一个保存，它看起来仍然一样。
give it a save and it still does look the same.
现在，好吧。
Now, okay.
现在让我们上到页面顶部。
Now let's go up to the top of the page.
现在在这里，我们可能需要一些空间
And now here, we probably need some space
在这个标题和这个 H2 元素之间，对吧？
between this header and this H2 element here, right?
所以这看起来很糟糕。
So this looks very bad.
所以我们需要在这个元素之外有一些空间。
And so we need some space outside of this element here.
所以在这两者之间，为此，
So between these two, and for that,
我们可以在下方使用边距底部，
we can use a margin bottom below,
基本上这个标题元素。
basically this header element.
所以让我们来到我们的主要标题
So let's come here to our main header
假设边缘底部为 60 像素。
and at a margin bottom of let's say, 60 pixels.
而事实上，
And it is in fact,
很常见，主要使用底部的空间
very common to use mostly space at the bottom
为了创造垂直空间。
in order to create vertical space.
好的。
Okay.
所以只要坚持到任何一个边距顶部
So just a stick to either margin top
或总是边缘底部。
or always margin bottom.
所以其中一个很好，
So one of them is fine,
但最好不要总是在需要时混合它们
but it's best not to always mix them when you want
在元素之间创建空间
to create space between elements
就个人而言，我真的很喜欢使用margin bottom。
and personally, I really like to use margin bottom.
在我看来，这样做很有意义。
It makes a lot of sense in my mind to do it like this.
好的，让我们继续。
Okay and let's keep going.
也许现在在这个 H2 下方添加一些空间。
And maybe add some space now, below this H2.
所以H2就在这里。
So H2 is right here.
所以让我们再说一次底部的边距，
So let's say a margin at the bottom, once again,
在这里我们只使用 30 个像素。
and here we just use 30 pixels.
同样，这里的这些值是非常随机的
And again, these values here are quite random
稍后我们将使用一个系统来自动，
and later we will use a system to automatically,
基本上为我们创造了这些价值。
basically create these values for us.
接下来，让我们在这部分之间创建一些空间。
Next, let's create some space here between this part.
所以基本上是这张图片，然后是其余的内容。
So basically this image and then the rest of the content.
如果我们看一下我们的标记，
And if we take a look at our markup,
那部分，所以这张图片，这个作者，
that part, so this image, this author,
这里的另一个图像是这个标题。
and this other image here is this header.
因此，让我们在此标题的底部添加一些边距。
So let's add some margin bottom to this header.
所以我给它起了另一个名字。
And so I'm giving it another name.
所以这个是主要的标题。
So this one is the main header.
所以让我们在这里称它为帖子标题。
So let's call this one here, the post header.
所以让我们复制到这里，
So let's copy that here,
放在这里，
put it here,
然后边距底部 40 像素。
and then margin bottom of 40 pixels.
所以这要好得多。
So that's a lot nicer.
接下来，我想考虑段落
Next, I want to think about the paragraphs
因为，好吧，现在看起来很乱。
because, well, this looks very messy right now.
所以只需在底部添加一些空间
And so just by adding some space to the bottom
每个段落，
of each paragraph,
这将使它立即变得更好。
that will make it a lot better immediately.
所以边距底部，让我们在这里尝试 15 像素。
So margin bottom, and let's try 15 pixels here.
事实上，这已经好多了。
And indeed that is a lot better already.
现在与这些列表相同。
Now the same with these lists.
所以现在在这里，在这个有序列表中
So now here, in this ordered list
还有我们这里的无序列表，
and this unordered list that we have here,
现在，实际上数字和要点已经消失了。
now, actually the numbers and the bullet points are a gone.
那是因为我们实际上需要一些空间
And that is because we actually need some space
在左侧，以便可以显示它们。
on the left side so that they can be shown.
所以让我们把它们加回来，因为，
So let's add them back because,
我们的全局重置，基本上删除了所有这些空间。
our global reset, basically removed all those spaces.
记住？
Remember?
所以我们想要无序列表中的那个空间
So we want that space in the unordered list
并且也在有序列表中。
and also in the ordered list.
所以让我们说左边的边距，
So let's say margin on the left side,
例如，
for example,
一个 50 像素。
a 50 pixel.
所以现在你看到了，他们回来了。
And so now you see that, they are back.
所以一切都向右移动了 50 个像素。
So everything moved 50 pixels to the right.
所以现在是那个，所以数字和项目符号又回来了。
And so now the one, so the numbers and the bullets are back.
让我们在底部添加一些空间，
Let's also add some space to the bottom,
20 像素。
20 pixels.
好的。
Okay.
现在让我们继续讨论 H3。
And now let's move on to the H3.
所以这就是这里。
So that's this one here.
所以边距底部 20 像素，
So margin bottom 20 pixels,
出了点问题。
and something is wrong.
我显然不能拼写margin。
I cannot spell margin apparently.
所以看起来好多了。
So that looks a lot better.
现在我们还需要指定一些距离
And now we also need to specify some distance
在此文本和此标题之间。
between this text here and this heading.
所以现在看起来，
So right now it looks like,
这两者之间的空间是完全一样的
the space between these two is exactly the same
这不好。
and that's not good.
我实际上正在这样做
And I'm actually doing this
因为我想给你看一些东西。
because I want to show you something.
所以我现在要指定边距顶部
So I'm gonna specify the margin top now
并将其设置为 40 像素。
and set it to 40 pixels.
好的。现在效果很好。
Okay. Now that works beautifully.
但是，现在让我向您展示一些使用开发工具的东西。
However, let me now show you something using the dev tools.
所以我正在检查这个元素。
So I'm inspecting this element.
所以你看到正好有 20 个像素
And so you see that there is exactly the 20 pixels
那是我们在底部指定的，
that'd we specified to the bottom,
以及我们指定到顶部的 40 个像素。
and the 40 pixels that we specified to the top.
然而，在它之前的这段，
However, this paragraph that comes before it,
其实底部也有边距，
actually also has a margin to the bottom of,
我相信，15像素。
I believe, 15 pixels.
所以这个，对吧？
So this one, right?
所以现在这个元素到顶部有 40 像素
So right now this element here has 40 pixels to the top
这个底部有 15 个像素。
and this one has 15 pixels to the bottom.
所以这两个空间都占据了这个区域，对吧？
And so both of these spaces occupy this area here, right?
所以我们可能会直觉地认为，
And so we might intuitively think that,
这两个空间确实加起来了。
these two spaces do get added up.
所以基本上，这15个像素将被添加
So basically that, these 15 pixels here will get added
到来自这里的 40 个像素。
to the 40 pixels that come from here.
但在 f行动，这不是发生的事情。
But in fact, that is not what happens.
所以我们在这里看到事实上，
So we see here that in fact,
两个元素之间的距离
the distance between the two elements
真的只有40像素。
is really just 40 pixels.
它不是 55 像素。
It is not 55 pixels.
好的。
Okay.
这种现象被称为边缘收缩。
And this phenomena is called collapsing margins.
所以基本上，
So basically,
当我们有两个占据相同空间的边距时，
when we have two margins that occupied the same space,
只有其中一个在页面上实际可见。
only one of them is actually visible on the page.
这通常是两者中较大的一个。
And that is usually the larger of the two.
例如，
So for example,
假设我们指定了，比如这里的 40 像素。
let's say that we specified, like 40 pixels here.
那么我们可能会认为，
Then we might've thought that,
这实际上是 80 像素，
this was actually 80 pixels here,
所以遵循与之前相同的逻辑。
so following the same logic from before.
但当然它仍然只有 40 像素
But of course it is still only 40 pixels
因为边距塌陷。
because of the collapsing margins.
但是如果我们在这里有 100 个像素呢？
But what if we had like 100 pixels here?
那么，现在这里的空间实际上是 100 像素。
Well then, now the space here would in fact be 100 pixels.
所以正是你在那里看到的这个橙色空间。
So exactly this orange space that you see right there.
对？
Right?
所以这个现在还有40个，
So this one now still has its 40,
但是这个有一百个。
but this one has a hundred.
所以现在他们之间的距离还不是140，
And so now the space between them is still not 140,
但它是&lt;p&gt;底部的这一百个像素。
but it's these hundred pixels of the bottom of the &lt;p&gt;.
好的。
Okay.
所以这就是我们说话时的意思
So this is what we mean when we talk
关于折叠边距，
about collapsing margins,
这是你可能会听到的
which is something that you might hear
一旦你开始听到人们谈论一些 CSS，
once you start hearing people talking about some CSS,
奇怪的怪癖或类似 CSS 内部的奇怪东西。
weird quirks or like weird stuff that is inside of CSS.
好的。
Okay.
而且，但是，我认为我们基本上已经完成了。
And, but this, I think we are basically almost done already.
让我们在这里添加更多空间
Let's just add some more space here
在这些相关帖子和所有这些内容之间，
between these related posts and all this content here,
哪个是文章，对吧？
which is the article, right?
所以我们有文章和&lt;aside&gt;。
So we have article and the &lt;aside&gt;.
所以我们也需要一些空间。
So we need some space there as well.
而且我不认为我是否已经在任何地方选择了这篇文章
And I don't think if I already selected the article anywhere
看起来我没有，
and it looks like I didn't,
所以让我们把它放在顶部。
so let's put that at the top.
既然我在这里，
And since I'm here,
我将抓住这个导航并将其也放在顶部
I will grab this nav and put it also at the top
因为它是那些更大的元素之一。
because it's one of those bigger elements.
所以我喜欢让他们保持在顶部。
So I like to keep them at the top.
当然，这篇文章也是如此。
And of course the same goes for the article.
所以文章，
So article,
和一个很好的 60 像素边距底部。
and a nice margin bottom of 60 pixel.
好的。
Okay.
现在我们开始，
And here we go,
就是这样，这是我们的页面讨厌的格式
that's it, that's our page nasty formatted
在边距和填充方面。
in terms of margins and paddings.
所以只是快速回顾一下，
So just to quickly recap,
每当您需要元素内部的一些空间时，
whenever you need some space inside of an element,
这是非常有用的，
which is very useful,
主要是当有背景颜色时
mostly when there is a background color
或元素上的边框，
or a border on the element,
那么你总是使用填充。
then you always use padding.
另一方面，
On the other hand,
为了在元素之外创造空间，
in order to create space outside of an element,
或者也可以在多个元素之间创建空间，
or also to create space between multiple elements,
始终使用边距。
always use margin.
如果您需要添加垂直空间，
And in case that you need to add vertical space,
那么我建议你大部分时间，
then I advise you to most of the time,
坚持边距底部。
stick to margin bottom.
所以基本上这就是增加空间
And so basically that's it about adding space
到我们的页面元素。
to our page elements.
而在接下来的讲座中，
And in the next lecture,
然后我们还将添加尺寸，例如高度和宽度。
we will then also add dimensions, so height and width.